<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chandigarh Guide</string>
    <string name="default_string">Hello Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="default_address">Sukhna Lake</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="attraction1_name">Rock Garden</string>
    <string name="attraction2_name">Sukhna Lake</string>
    <string name="attraction3_name">Rose Garden</string>
    <string name="attraction4_name">Elante Mall</string>
    <string name="attraction5_name">Le Corbusier Centre</string>
    <string name="attraction6_name">Sukhna Wildlife Century</string>
    <string name="attraction7_name">Mohali Cricket Stadium</string>
    <string name="attraction1_address">Sector 1, Chandigarh 160001</string>
    <string name="attraction2_address">Sector 1, Chandigarh, 160001</string>
    <string name="attraction3_address">Jan Marg, 16B, Sector 16, Chandigarh, 160016</string>
    <string name="attraction4_address">178-178A, Purv Marg, Industrial Area Phase I, Chandigarh, 160002</string>
    <string name="attraction5_address">Old Architect Building, Sector 19B, Madhya Marg, Chandigarh, 160019</string>
    <string name="attraction6_address">North-East Of Sukhna Lake, Chandigarh, India</string>
    <string name="attraction7_address">Phase 9, Sector 63, Sahibzada Ajit Singh Nagar, Chandigarh 160063</string>
    <string name="attraction1_description">Located in sector 1 of the beautiful city Chandigarh, The Rock Garden has been designed as an open-air exhibition hall using urban and industrial wastes by Nek Chand, a former Road Inspector in Chandigarh. Also known as Neck Chand\'s Rock Garden, this massive 40-acre garden is a colourful mosaic of art pieces and sculptures</string>
    <string name="attraction2_description">Nestled at the foothills of Shivaliks, Sukhna Lake is a beautiful lake set amid the picturesque surroundings of Chandigarh. Stretching for a distance of 3 kilometres, the Sukhna Lake is a man-made lake and is one of its kind in the city created in the year 1958</string>
    <string name="attraction3_description">Located in sector 16 of Chandigarh, Rose Garden is a blooming garden which showcases nature at its best. The garden is spread over a massive area of 30 acres and is packed with an exquisite variety of flowers making it quite popular among tourists</string>
    <string name="attraction4_description">Elante Mall is a shopping mall in the city of Chandigarh in India. With the gross leasable area of 1,150,000 sq ft, it is the second largest shopping mall in Northern India and the eleventh largest in India</string>
    <string name="attraction5_description">Le Corbusier Centre is a popular heritage spot in the city of Chandigarh, situated at Sector 19B and dedicated to the ancient architect of the city- Le Corbusier</string>
    <string name="attraction6_description">The Sukhna Wildlife Sanctuary is a protected wildlife sanctuary. It is just 2 kilometers from the Sukhna Lake. It has been spread over an area of 26 square kilometres ( 2600 hectares ) of forest land spanning the plains at the foot of the Shivalik Hills</string>
    <string name="attraction7_description">The Punjab Cricket Association IS Bindra Stadium (Punjabi: ਪੰਜਾਬ ਕ੍ਰਿਕੇਟ ਐਸੋਸੀਏਸ਼ਨ ਆਈਐਸ ਬਿੰਦਰਾ ਸਟੇਡੀਅਮ) is a cricket ground located in Mohali, Chandigarh CR. It is popularly referred to as the Mohali Stadium</string>
    <string name="places1_name">Pinjore gardens</string>
    <string name="places2_name">Museum and Art Gallery</string>
    <string name="places3_name">Nada Sahib Gurudwara</string>
    <string name="places4_name">International Dolls Museum</string>
    <string name="places5_name">Chattbir Zoo</string>
    <string name="places6_name">Terraced Garden</string>
    <string name="places7_name">Cactus Garden</string>
    <string name="places1_address">Ambala-Shimla Highway, Pinjore, Haryana 134102</string>
    <string name="places2_address">Jan Marg, Near Matka Chowk, Sector 10C, Chandigarh, 160011</string>
    <string name="places3_address">NH 7, Nada Sahib Road, Sector 22, Panchkula, Haryana 134109</string>
    <string name="places4_address">Bal Bhawan, Udyog Path, Sector 23B, Chandigarh, 160023</string>
    <string name="places5_address">Chattbir Zoo Rd, Chhat, Punjab 140603</string>
    <string name="places6_address">Sector 33B, Sector 33, Chandigarh, 160032</string>
    <string name="places7_address">Panchkula Urban Estate, Sector 5, Budanpur, Panchkula, Haryana 134108</string>
    <string name="places1_description">Spread over a massive area of 100 acres and also known as Yadvinder Garden, Pinjore Garden is a spectacle to behold.</string>
    <string name="places2_description">The Government Museum and Art Gallery is a natural history museum and an art gallery in Chandigarh. Established in August of 1947, the building was designed by the very noted architect, Le Corbusier.</string>
    <string name="places3_description">Nadu Shah Lubana family member of Baba Makhan Shah Lubana of the adjoining village served Guru Gobind Singh and his followers with food and milk.Guruji blessed Nadu Shah and said that due to his service the place would be known as Nada Sahib and his name will be remembered forever.</string>
    <string name="places4_description">Established in 1985 by Chandigarh  Rotary Club, and run by the city administration, the International Dolls Museum showcases dolls and puppets from around the world.></string>
    <string name="places5_description">Chhatbir Zoo (formally Mahendra Chaudhary Zoological Park), is a zoological park situated close to Zirakpur, India. The zoo was constructed in the 1970s and is home to a large variety of birds, mammals and reptiles.</string>
    <string name="places6_description">Illuminated musical fountain and the well planned orchard makes this 10 acre spread in Sector 33 an ideal picnic spot</string>
    <string name="places7_description">Sarkaria Cactus Garden is at a distance of 8 km from Panchkula in Chandigarh. It is located in Panchkula City’s heart, which covers total 7 acre area. This garden is largest botanical succulent garden of India.</string>
    <string name="rest1_name">Garlic And Greens</string>
    <string name="rest2_name">Virgin Courtyard</string>
    <string name="rest3_name">Cafe JC’s</string>
    <string name="rest4_name">Swagath Restaurant</string>
    <string name="rest5_name">Ghazal Restaurant</string>
    <string name="rest6_name">Shangrila</string>
    <string name="rest7_name"><![CDATA[Chilli & Pepper]]></string>
    <string name="rest1_address">Elante Mall, BBMB Industrial Area Phase 1, Purv Marg, Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="rest2_address">SCO 1A, Madhya Marg, Sector 7C, Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="rest3_address"><![CDATA[Shop No. 2 & 3, Coal Depot, Sector-10D, Chandigarh]]></string>
    <string name="rest4_address">SCO, Madhya Marg, Sector 26, Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="rest5_address">SCO 189-191, Sector 17 C, Sector 17, Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="rest6_address">SCO-324, Near Maya Hotel, Sector 35B, Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="rest7_address">Arista Hotel, SCO 1040A-1044 Sahibzada Ajit Singh Nagar</string>
    <string name="rest1_description">One of the most innovative veg restaurants in Chandigarh, Garlic and Greens has given a new meaning to vegetarian food. With its antiquated interiors, blissful environment, and a European style kitchen, it is the finest Italian restaurant in Chandigarh for vegetarians who wish to taste something unique.</string>
    <string name="rest2_description">With a rustic looking ambience, and an elegant outdoor seating, the Virgin Courtyard is one of the best romantic restaurants in Chandigarh. Savour mouth watering Italian cuisine in a tranquil countryside setting accompanied by fine wines, and a completely lit courtyard that makes your experience worth remembering.</string>
    <string name="rest3_description">Cafe JC’s is one of the top fine dining restaurants in Chandigarh that serves delicious Chinese Cuisine. Its elegant interiors and serene outdoor sitting create a perfect environment for an unforgettable dining experience that will make you come back to this place every now and then.</string>
    <string name="rest4_description">Much famed for its seafood, Swagath restaurant serves flavourful dishes of various cuisines with main focus on South Indian food. It is one of the best restaurants in Chandigarh known for its upmarket ambience, courteous staff, and elaborate menu.</string>
    <string name="rest5_description">Situated in the extremely popular Sector 17 market of Chandigarh, Ghazal restaurant serves the best local cuisine in town. With a graceful ambience, courteous staff, and finger licking punjabi food, it is one of the best restaurants near Chandigarh for a fine dining experience.</string>
    <string name="rest6_description">Dedicated to serving lip smacking chinese food, Shangri la is one of the best Chinese restaurants in Chandigarh. With a fairly large seating capacity and a contemporary ambience, it is one of the best restaurants in Chandigarh to dine out with your friends or family.</string>
    <string name="rest7_description"><![CDATA[Looking for buffet restaurants in Chandigarh? Located just a few kilometers away from Chandigarh, Chilli & Pepper is known for its elaborate buffet menu at extremely reasonable prices. With an upscale ambience, modish decors, and scrumptious food, it is one of the best restaurants near Chandigarh for family dining.]]></string>
    <string name="event1_name">Mobile Developer Fest(4-5 Oct)</string>
    <string name="event2_name">SunBurn 2018(15-16 Oct)</string>
    <string name="event3_name">Bacardi NH7 Weekender(5 Nov)</string>
    <string name="event4_name">Startup Weekend Chandigarh(28-30 Sept)</string>
    <string name="event1_address">UIET Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="event2_address">Sec 35A Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="event3_address">Bhullar Resort Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="event4_address">Chitkara University Rajpura</string>
    <string name="event1_description">Mobile Developer Fest (MDF) is an event series hosted by Google Developers in different college campuses across India for aspiring mobile developers. It offers hands-on training, speaker sessions across multiple product areas, and inspiring stories from Indian developers.</string>
    <string name="event2_description">Sunburn is amongst the world\'s biggest music festivals. In the past eleven years of its existence, Sunburn has brought together renowned Indian and international artists to entertain hundreds of thousands of dance music lovers through its various formats that reach out to fans across India</string>
    <string name="event3_description">Head to The Festive Hills, Thadlaskein, Lad Mukhla, Jaintia Hills to catch amazing live performances by artists from India and around the world, a bustling bazaar where you can get local finds, fashions and foods, fascinating</string>
    <string name="event4_description">Startup Weekend is a 54-hour event that brings together global Startup Entrepreneurs like designers, developers, Techies, and experts from all domains to do amazing things.</string>
</resources>